[Music]
[音乐]
this is Nick with logos by Nick comm and
我是尼克·康姆的标志尼克
in this tutorial I'll be giving you a
在本教程中，我将给您一个
brief overview of all 21 of Inkscape
Inkscape的所有21个简要概述
stools
凳子
I've even put together a written
我甚至还写了一份
overview that you can use for a quick
概述，您可以使用它快速了解
reference anytime you'd like I'll have a
任何时候你愿意，我都会有一个
link to that in the description of the
链接到描述中的
video and if you'd like a more in-depth
视频，如果您想要更深入地了解
explanation of these tools along with
这些工具的说明以及
every other feature in Inkscape be sure
Inkscape中的所有其他功能都要确保
to check out my Inkscape masterclass
查看我的Inkscape大师课
it's a collection of over 60 videos
这是60多个视频的集合
where I go over every tool and feature
在那里我检查了每一个工具和功能
in Inkscape and I explain what it is and
在Inkscape中，我解释了它是什么
demonstrate how it works
演示其工作原理
I'll have a link to that in the
我会在
description of the video as well let's
视频的描述也是如此，让我们
have a look at the Select tool to get us
了解一下选择工具，让我们
started because this is the tool that
开始是因为这是一个
you'll probably be using most often the
您可能会最常使用
Select tool as the name suggests allows
顾名思义，选择工具允许
you to select individual or multiple
您可以选择单个或多个
objects at a time you can also use it to
对象，您还可以使用它来
make some common transformation to your
对您的产品进行一些常见的转型
objects like scaling rotating and
对象，如缩放、旋转和
shearing
剪毛
the Edit paths by nodes tool allows you
您可以使用按结点编辑路径工具
to transform the structural properties
转换结构属性的步骤
of an object by altering the individual
通过改变个体来改变对象
coordinate points of that object
该对象的坐标点
otherwise known as nodes you can
也称为节点，您可以
reposition them add new nodes delete
重新定位它们添加新节点删除
nodes and even change node type whether
节点甚至更改节点类型是否
it be a sharp corner or a rounded edge
它是尖角还是圆边
the tool also allows you to change the
该工具还允许您更改
contours of an object's lines by
对象的线条的轮廓按
manually moving them or by adjusting the
手动移动它们或通过调整
handles of its nearest node
其最近节点的句柄
the squares and rectangles tool is used
使用正方形和矩形工具
to create four-sided vector objects
创建四边矢量对象的步骤
whether it be a rectangle or a perfectly
不管它是长方形还是完美的
symmetrical square by default your
默认情况下为对称正方形
rectangle will have sharp corners but
矩形将有尖锐的角，但
you can use the little round node at the
您可以在
top right to give you a rectangle of
右上角为您提供一个矩形
rounded corners you can easily switch
圆角，您可以轻松切换
back to sharp corners anytime you'd like
随时都可以回到急转弯
by clicking the make corners sharp
通过单击使拐角锐化
button in the tool settings menu
工具设置菜单中的按钮
the circles and ellipses tool is used to
圆和椭圆工具用于
create vector shapes with curved edges
创建具有弯曲边缘的矢量形状
like ellipses and perfectly round
像椭圆一样，完美地圆
circles it can also be used to create
它还可以用来创建圆
partial ellipses by maneuvering this
通过操纵这个来实现部分省略
circular handle at the right edge of the
控件右边缘的圆形手柄
shape keeping your cursor outside of the
将光标保持在
ellipse will allow you to change it by
Ellipse将允许您更改它
its radius whereas moving your cursor to
它的半径，而将光标移动到
the inside of the circle will allow you
圆圈的内侧可以让你
to change a by its diameter at any point
在任意点通过直径改变a
you can reset the shape back to being an
您可以将该形状重置为
ellipse in the tool settings menu
工具设置菜单中的椭圆
the stars and polygons tool is used to
星形和面工具用于
create multi-sided objects it's divided
创建被分割的多面对象
up into two separate functions one for
最多分为两个单独的函数，一个用于
stars and one for polygons
星形和一个用于多边形
when creating stars you'll be able to
当你创造星星的时候，你将能够
set the number of corners the star has
设置星形的角点数
the spoke ratio between each star and
每颗恒星与星体之间的轮辐比
you can choose to give your star rounded
你可以选择给你的明星四舍五入
corners as well if you'd like
如果你愿意的话，角落也可以。
when creating polygons you'll be able to
在创建面时，您将能够
set the number of sides and corners and
设置边数和角数，并
you can choose to make them round it if
在以下情况下，您可以选择让它们绕过它
you'd like this can all be done in the
你会希望这一切都可以在
tool settings menu or by manually
工具设置菜单或手动
adjusting the handles directly on the
直接在上调整手柄
canvas
帆布
the 3d boxes tool allows you to quickly
3D框工具允许您快速
create three-sided vector boxes that
创建具有以下特性的三边向量框
appear as if they're three-dimensional
看起来就像是三维的
the X Y and z-axis can be adjusted
可以调整X、Y和Z轴
independently in order to determine the
为了独立地确定
box's width height and depth the red
方框的宽度、高度和深度为红色
lines represent the height of the box
线条表示框的高度
the blue lines represent the width of
蓝色线条表示
the box and the yellow lines represent
方框和黄线代表
the box's depth you can also change the
长方体的深度您还可以更改
perspective of the box by moving the
通过移动长方体
nodes associated with the red and yellow
与红色和黄色相关联的节点
lines
线条
the spirals tool is used to create
螺旋线工具用于创建
vector objects that follow a spiral path
沿螺旋路径的矢量对象
the tool allows you to adjust the number
该工具允许您调整数字
of turns the spiral has as well as its
螺旋线的转弯次数以及它的
divergence from its center point this
偏离其中心点这一点
can be done either in the tool settings
可在工具设置中完成
menu or directly on the canvas
菜单或直接在画布上
the Bezier pen is used for manually
Bezier钢笔用于手动
drawing your own vector shapes by
通过以下方式绘制您自己的矢量形状
creating a series of nodes and lines you
创建一系列的节点和线
can make both straight and curved lines
既可以做直线，也可以做曲线
as well as sharpen rounded corners the
除了锐化圆角之外，
tool also has a variety of settings
该工具还具有多种设置
built in including spiral paths and B
内置包括缓和曲线路径和B
splines each of which determines how the
样条线，每条样条线都决定了
pen behaves they can be used to force
笔的行为可以用来强制
any behavior you'd like
任何你喜欢的行为
including curved lines rounded corners
包括曲线和圆角
parallel lines and more
平行线和更多
the free hand lines tool functions much
手绘线条工具功能强大
like the Bezier pen only it allows you
就像贝塞尔钢笔一样，只是它让你
to draw your shapes with your hands
用手画出你的形状
movement as opposed to clicking to
移动，而不是点击
create a bunch of nodes this would make
创建一组节点，这将使
it more ideal if you were using a
如果您使用的是
drawing tablet or some kind of stylus
绘图板或某种手写笔
much like the Bezier pen the freehand
就像贝塞尔笔下的写意笔
aligns tool has various settings built
对齐工具构建了各种设置
in that will dictate the tools behavior
这将决定工具的行为
the calligraphy pen allows you to create
书法笔可以让你创作
freehand vector objects using a classic
使用经典的手绘向量对象
brushstroke and shape of your choosing
笔触和形状由您选择
the tool has various presets built-in
该工具具有内置的各种预设
that will determine the size and shape
这将决定它的大小和形状
of your brushstrokes there's also a
在你的笔触中，还有一个
variety of settings that you can tweak
您可以调整的各种设置
to dictate how the tool will behave
指定该工具的行为方式
the text objects tool is used to create
文本对象工具用于创建
vector text and wording of your choosing
您选择的矢量文本和措辞
it allows you to flow your text into a
它允许您将文本排成一个
bounding box or simply generate it all
边界框或简单地全部生成
on a single line you can also use the
在一行中，您还可以使用
tool settings to adjust the font size
用于调整字体大小的工具设置
orientation spacing between letters and
字母之间的方向间距和
words as well as various other
单词以及其他各种
adjustments
调整
the gradients tool allows you to color
渐变工具允许您对颜色
your objects with multiple colors that
您的对象具有多种颜色，
fade into each other otherwise known as
淡入彼此，也称为
gradients the tool allows you to edit
渐变该工具允许您编辑
your gradients based on colors used
基于所用颜色的渐变
number of colors and the position of the
颜色的数量和位置
color is relative to the object that
颜色是相对于
it's being applied to the gradients can
它被应用于渐变可以
follow either a straight linear path or
沿着一条直线路径或
a rounded radio
圆形收音机
the mesh's tool functions similarly to
网格工具的功能类似于
the gradients tool only it allows you to
渐变工具仅允许您执行以下操作
give your objects a gradient that
为您的对象提供一个渐变
follows either a grid otherwise known as
遵循网格，也称为
a mesh gradient or a cone otherwise
网格渐变或圆锥体
known as a conical gradient you can use
称为圆锥渐变，您可以使用
the tool to manually alter the points of
用于手动更改的点的工具
your meshes and cones directly on the
将网格和圆锥体直接放置在
canvas
帆布
the pick colors from an image tool
从图像拾取颜色工具
commonly referred to as the dropper
通常被称为滴管
allows you to set an object's filling
允许您设置对象的填充
stroke color based on another object's
基于另一个对象的笔触颜色
color the tool allows you to sample
该工具允许您对颜色进行采样
colors from both vector objects and
来自矢量对象和
rasterized images your selected object
栅格化的图像您所选的对象
will be filled with whatever color you
都会被你的任何颜色填满
sample from the other object you can
您可以从其他对象获取样本
also hold shift while sampling to set
在采样时同时按住Shift键也可以设置
the selection as your objects stroke
对象描边时的选定内容
color you can also click and drag to
您还可以单击并拖动的颜色
create a selection that the tool will
创建该工具将使用的选区
use to generate an average color of the
用于生成
colors in that area
那个区域的颜色
the fill bounded areas tool commonly
填充有界区域工具通常
referred to as the bucket tool allows
称为铲斗工具允许
you to fill empty spaces with the
来填充空白区域。
predetermined fill color in order for
预定的填充颜色，按顺序
the tool to work the area you're filling
用于处理您正在填充的区域的工具
in must be completely surrounded by a
In必须完全由一个
closed path it will not work on empty
闭合路径在空路径上不起作用
spaces that bleed out into the open
血流成河的开阔空间
canvas the tool will reference whatever
画布该工具将引用任何
you have set as the fill and Stroke
您已设置为填充和描边
color for filling in your objects
用于填充对象的颜色
the tweak objects tool allows you to
调整对象工具允许您执行以下操作
make compound alterations to multiple
对多个项进行复合更改
objects pads and colors all at once
对象、衬垫和颜色同时出现
alterations include moving multiple
更改包括移动多个
objects at once shrinking them rotating
对象一次缩小它们的旋转
them or duplicating them it also allows
它们或复制它们也允许
you to make adjustments based on colors
您可以根据颜色进行调整
and blurs
和模糊
the spray objects tool allows you to
喷射对象工具允许您执行以下操作
generate multiple objects by spraying
通过喷雾生成多个对象
them onto your canvas the objects that
把它们放到你的画布上
are sprayed is determined by the object
被喷洒的是由物体决定的
you have selected at the moment the tool
此时您已经选择了该工具
has a variety of settings that will
具有各种设置，可以
allow you to adjust certain behaviors
允许您调整某些行为
like whether or not the objects overlap
例如对象是否重叠
the size of the scatter area whether or
散布区域的大小，无论是
not to rotate the sprayed objects and
不旋转喷洒的物体和
more
更多
the eraser tool is used to delete
橡皮擦工具用于删除
segments of a vector path in a freestyle
自由式中的矢量路径段
technique that is based on your hands
以你的双手为基础的技术
movement the tool can work on multiple
移动该工具可以在多个
objects at a time and it has a variety
对象，并且它有各种各样的
of settings built-in that will allow you
内置设置，可让您
to dictate how the tool behaves it
指定该工具的行为方式
should be noted though that this tool
但应该注意的是，该工具
only work on vector paths it won't work
只在矢量路径上工作，它不会工作
on text objects and rasterized images
关于文本对象和光栅化图像
the diagram connectors tool allows you
逻辑示意图连接符工具允许您
to create diagrams by generating pads
通过生成焊盘来创建图表
and boxes that link objects together
以及将对象链接在一起的框
much like every other tool it has a
就像它拥有的所有其他工具一样
variety of settings built-in that allows
各种内置设置，允许
you to dictate how the tool behaves
您可以决定该工具的行为方式
whether it be avoiding selected objects
无论它是在避免选定对象
or ignoring selected objects
或忽略选定对象
the zoom tool allows you to increase or
缩放工具允许您增加或
decrease your view of the canvas you can
尽可能缩小您的画布视图
zoom in to see fine details zoom out to
放大以查看详细信息缩小至
get a more complete view of the canvas
获得更完整的画布视图
or set the view ratio to one-to-one in
或将视图比例设置为1：1
order to see how the canvas looks at
以查看画布的外观
full size
全尺寸
the measurement tool allows you to
测量工具允许您
measure any object based on its length
根据物体的长度测量任何物体
width height radius or diameter it
宽度、高度、半径或直径
allows you to choose from a variety of
允许您从各种不同的
measurement units including pixels
测量单位，包括像素
inches centimeters millimeters and more
英寸、厘米、毫米和更多
the tool also has a setting built-in
该工具还具有内置设置
that allows you to convert your
这使您可以将您的
measurement into an object that you can
测量到一个对象，你可以
work with further and export as a
与进一步合作，并作为
graphic of its own
它自己的图形
and that should do it for all of
这对所有人来说都应该是可行的
Inkscape stools as a version 1.0 if you
Inkscape可以作为1.0版使用，如果
have any questions leave a comment below
如果有任何问题，请在下面留下评论
and as always thanks for watching
一如既往地感谢您的收看
you
你